sup everyone tamera's running five here
with a very special video today when i'm
bored of taking a [ __ ] there is nothing
more than i love than to read through
the official sonic underground danny's
activity book you know denny's the
pancake place my parents would always
take me there when i was a kid and [ __ ]
even made my own sundays too with cherry
syrup and all that
anyway i was flipping through it playing
some games when i landed on this maze
sonic and knuckles makes me exact i was
playing it and
well maybe maybe i should just show you
first off you need to know the rules
rule number one you cannot touch a swap
bar if you do you're [ __ ] and two the
only of the only other rule you cannot
trace over any land you just made got it
all right here we go this is going to
piss you off
and i'm sure as
much as soccer is good
all right everyone here we go first i'll
go this way look at this
i'll go up here top right boom gothia
guitar
look at that i'll go left now i'm going
down i'll be killing swapbot
oh i got the drum set now to go oh wait
look
i can't go there [ __ ] because i would
trace the path
so rerun
okay i'll go get i'll go get the
keyboard so i get that i think okay i
got this i was going to get the drums
but i i can't see
i can't do it i got the drones but then
i go back here i'm stuck again so i
rewind
and think okay
maybe i'll get the drumsticks
and then i get them but then i realize i
can't go that way either
what the [ __ ] is this
i mean so i go i'm maybe i'll go up and
then i'll get like the keyboard
then i got one i'll go to the rap boom
gotta get the drums
i got that and i go over to the top
right got the catal boom
left
i can go that way there's a swap bar
there's a keyboard
damn
what the [ __ ] do i do
look at this
so okay i think okay maybe i'll go get
the drumsticks
and it's not working because there's a
swap bot up there
and then i realize if i go
down i'm
i'm back look at that i can't go there
because i retrace my line
like is the drumsticks in an unreachable
area
look at that there is no way to get out
get that one
look the the rules say i have to go
there though
the rules say i can't retrace my lines
are you kidding this is worse than
cyberpunk 2017